{
  "level": 4,
  "unit": 5,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Something _____________ is usual or normal for that person, thing, or group",
          "answer": "typical"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ is to stick closely.",
          "answer": "cling"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ is to mix with a liquid and become part of the liquid.",
          "answer": "dissolves"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something _____________ contains very small bits of sand or stone.",
          "answer": "gritty"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means “moist” or “full of water vapor.”",
          "answer": "humid"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ is to make something look bigger than it really is.",
          "answer": "magnify"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a device for looking at things that are too small to be seen with the naked eye.",
          "answer": "microscope"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ is to mix or come together.",
          "answer": "mingle"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ means to turn or spin around rapidly",
          "answer": "whirl"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means hard to please and picky.",
          "answer": "Fussy"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ means to say or show something.",
          "answer": "express"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ means to surround or form a circle around.",
          "answer": "encircle"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An _____________ is a strong feeling such as love, hate, happiness, sorrow, or fear.",
          "answer": "emotion"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a bunch of picked flowers.",
          "answer": "bouquet"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ are pictures of people, usually showing only the face and upper part of the body.",
          "answer": "portraits"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that _____________ shines in quick, bright flashes.",
          "answer": "sparkles"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ something is to discover it, or make it known.",
          "answer": "uncover"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is _____________ is very large or great.",
          "answer": "tremendous"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ something means to keep a record.",
          "answer": "document"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the study of the way humans lived a long time ago.",
          "answer": "Archaeology"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An _____________ is a period of time in history, often starting with an important event.",
          "answer": "era"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is proof of something.",
          "answer": "Evidence"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An _____________ is a journey made for a particular reason.",
          "answer": "expedition"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To be _____________ means to last a long time without changing.",
          "answer": "permanent"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
